SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
Alex's job handover is almost complete.
The headquarters will have
a say regarding the appointment
of the next marketing manager.
We need to begin hiring now
to fill up the empty slots he left behind.
Who did he bring with him?
Annie. Ethan.
They have talked to me.
What about Shang Zhitao?
She hasn't spoken to me.
You care a lot about her.
I remember when she just joined,
you kept asking her to resign.
What? Finally noticed her talents?
Yes.
She is talented.
I want to keep her here.
As per our company's SOP,
HR is supposed to talk
to those who plan to leave
to understand their dissatisfaction
before persuading them to stay.
If only you knew then what you know now.
LOVE IS MAKING EXCEPTIONS
Is it very serious?
The patient fainted from hypoglycemia
due to not eating on time
and overworking.
His body just collapsed.
We will ask him to stay here for a while.
Make sure he eats properly
- and rests well.
- Okay. Okay.
Sir.
My brother works too hard.
Can you exaggerate his condition a bit?
I want him to rest here
for a few more days.
He's staying here no matter what.
As for how many days,
it depends on his recovery.
That's all.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Doctor.
Thanks.
Is Zhu all right?
He's fine.
Anyway,
I told the doctor that I was his sister
so that he could stay longer here
and rest.
Don't tell him.
Okay.
You made the right decision.
Let's check on him.
- This ward?
- Yes.
Why are you sitting up?
Tao, how come you're here?
What do you think?
I'm fine.
It's just that I didn't eat and fainted.
How embarrassing.
It is embarrassing. You're an adult
who fainted from starvation.
Zhu. This might sound harsh.
Work is important,
but your health is what lets you work.
I know.
I accept your opinion.
I promise that I'll eat
on time from now on.
This won't happen again.
Swear now.
Perhaps you guys should head back first?
You have work tomorrow.
Kicking us out already?
The doctor said if you neglected
your health again,
you would be sent here.
Yes.
We'll be going then.
Leave him be.
Rest well.
Drive safe.
I am your dad.
I raised you.
Is it wrong to ask you to repay me now?
INPATIENT ONE
Mom.
Didn't I just transfer
5,000 yuan to you last month?
All gone already?
Dad bet on horses again?
Mom, stop saying you're going to die.
If he hits you, call the police.
If that doesn't work, run away.
Call the police.
Don't worry about the money.
Let me finish my work first.
Yuanzhu.
Guess what I brought you.
Claypot rice porridge.
Eat while it's warm.
Take a seat.
As you know, Alex resigned.
I arranged the meeting today
to have a conversation with you.
What would you like to talk about?
How's your work lately? Too much?
Do you have to work overtime?
Unless it's urgent,
I don't usually work overtime.
I do have weekends to myself.
What do you usually do during weekends?
Weekends?
Give me an example.
For example…
For example,
I'll hang out with my friends.
We go shopping, drink coffee,
and enjoy the sun.
Are you seeing anyone now?
No.
Great.
A junior of mine just came back.
He's three years older than you.
He's quite nice
and is from a decent family.
Should I introduce him to you?
Are you happy with the career growth
we have given you?
Yes.
Flora, if Alex has given you an offer,
I hope you will turn him down.
In a new company,
your short-term salary increase
comes with a high risk.
Staying with us
allows you to be the top player
in the industry.
Your bosses can always change.
Only your capability
will make you stand out.
As Luke has said,
we have our own training program
and growth option.
As long as you work hard,
you can start from a normal staff member
and become the general manager.
Additionally, our remuneration
is among the most competitive ones,
and you will receive yearly increments.
This year, we intend
to increase your salary range.
Tracy also mentioned to me
that your performance was highly valued
in the workplace evaluation.
I personally have seen your sacrifices,
dedication, and growth.
I agree with the evaluation.
So I hope
you can stay and work together with us.
Thank you.
Thank you, Luke.
When I joined Lime,
I knew I was quite plain and average.
It was by sheer luck
that I managed to stay here.
I am grateful for everything I have now.
I…
I love the work ambiance here.
I love the people here.
And I know I have yet
to learn many things.
So,
Tracy,
Luke,
I will stay at Lime.
I'll take my leave then.
You two can discuss
the range of the increments.
Flora. Your honesty is much appreciated.
I was about to use my last bargaining chip
to convince you to stay.
What is it?
When Luke's scandal broke out,
you and Lumi came to me to attest for him.
Do you still remember that?
Yes.
There was an investigation,
but the result was not made public.
Because Luke chose
not to pursue it further.
It involved Alex.
It's all in the past now.
I just wanted to remind you
that even if you're leaving,
make sure you know
who you're leaving with.
Noted.
How did the recruitment go?
We vetted through the resumes.
Once the first interview is done,
I'll schedule
the second interview with you.
Are you seeing anyone now? Great.
A junior of mine just came back.
Should I introduce him to you?
Now I know why your division failed
to notice someone
was poaching our manager.
Why?
You're too busy setting up dates
for your employees to work.
It was just a friendly chit-chat.
Why are you so serious?
Relax.
I am relaxed.
But you guys might be too relaxed.
Fine. I can't win in an argument
against you.
You win.
Flora.
Do you have time for a stroll?
Sure.
I'm happy that you're staying.
I mean what I said today.
I'm sorry to have called you cheap
and obedient.
I was just describing
what my thinking process would be
if I were a manager
trying to poach other staff members.
I didn't mince my words.
I…
I did say a lot of things
out of spite too.
But when I reflected upon myself,
I realized some of your advice was good,
just a bit harsh.
I accept your apology
because I know you are a gentleman.
You have never bad-mouthed Alex.
I know I can be blunt, but I mean well.
If whatever I say ever upsets you,
you can tell me right away.
Don't block me.
Dealing with it is quite exhausting.
Then can you…
praise me more?
Luan Nian.
I need your encouragement.
I love it when you speak to me nicely.
Okay.
More encouragement and compliments.
I'll take note.
Do you want to eat something?
I want to eat meat
and drink a little bit. Just a little bit.
No. You bite when you're drunk.
No. I have never bitten anyone.
So when are you going to unblock me?
I'll unblock you when you buy me drinks.
Here. Come in, Guo.
What are you?
How come you have the keys to my home?
I am an agent.
The owner of this flat wants to sell it.
I brought a client to view it.
You must be the tenant.
Move out quickly.
- Wait.
- Come in.
You must have gotten something wrong.
The owner of this property is Zhang Lei.
And Ms. Zhou is Zhang Lei's ex-wife.
She is also a co-owner of this property.
She has the property ownership certificate
and the sales and purchase agreement.
She has authorized us
to handle this property.
Please move out quickly.
Guo, let's go inside.
The layout is good.
It is.
Lei,
an agent said your ex-wife
would be selling the flat.
He brought someone to view the property.
- It's not bad, right?
- Yes.
Check out that place.
‪It looks good.
Tao. I'm so sorry.
My ex-wife lost a lot of money in her
investment and needs money urgently.
She appointed an agent behind my back.
Once I finish my work,
I'll buy a ticket and fly back.
Do not fight them.
Let me handle it when I'm there.
Okay, Lei.
Hurry up.
Okay.
My client is happy with this place.
I need this property
to be vacant in two days.
Please move out soon.
Guo. Let's talk at the shop
near the entrance.
Come.
Move out now.
What do we do?
We can't find a place on short notice.
Don't worry.
Wait for Lei to come back,
and we'll figure this out.
Yuanzhu.
Discharged already?
Are you sure you're okay?
Did Lei tell you about the eviction?
Lei already talked to his ex-wife.
We're not moving.
We're not?
It's okay now.
That's great.
I knew it. The matter can be solved.
The most important lesson for those
who come to Beijing, eviction.
This is my third home.
If we truly are evicted,
we'll find a place together.
Right?
Don't worry.
GUAANZHUANG STATION
Why is it so cold here?
A power cut?
What happened?
Sun Yu.
That jerk of an agent must have done this.
- Let me talk to him.
- Don't.
We don't have proof that they did it.
They did this to make us move out.
They are bullying us.
Tenants have rights too.
They think they are above the law?
Come. Let's confront them.
Yuanzhu.
Someone trashed our home.
Wait for us at the entrance.
Let's head to the management office
and get the security footage.
Okay.
Lei.
- Lei.
- You're finally here.
Where are you going?
Someone broke our window
and cut off our power supply.
I'm sure the real estate agency
by the entrance did it.
We're planning to get
the security footage.
They broke the window?
Are you two okay?
- I'm fine.
Those hooligans.
Let's check the security footage.
If they did do it,
we'll report to the police.
- The one over there?
- Yes.
That one.
Yuanzhu.
You're right on time. Come.
What?
Don't stop us.
We checked the security footage.
This agency broke our window.
I demand compensation from them.
Girls, you'll wait outside.
Yuanzhu is right.
Even though we notified the police,
we must make sure you are safe as well.
Take this.
- Okay.
- We'll go in first.
- Wait for us here.
- Do not fight.
- Be civilized.
- Let's go.
Be civilized.
- Where's your manager?
- He's not here.
- Like I said, he's not here.
- Who broke my window?
- Just leave.
Broke what window?
Are you looking for a fight?
- How dare you?
- Dare what?
- What are you doing?
- You broke my window.
- No, I did not.
- Who broke my window?
- Are they fighting now?
- This soon?
Put those girls in a gunny sack.
- What did you just say?
- Did you touch me?
Did you push me?
How dare you threaten us?
- I'll call the police.
- You…
You… Stop!
You…
Bugger off!
- Stop!
- Run!
- Tao. Are you okay?
- I'm done with you!
- Throwing punches now?
Die!
- Stop! Stop it.
- Stop.
Stop. Do you hear me?
Stop now.
- They started it.
- Are you okay?
- They hit us.
- They did it first.
- He hit me.
- Are you all right?
- Officer. He hit me.
- They started it.
- Bring them back.
- Are you okay?
Come with me for the deposition.
FEBRUARY 14TH, UNITE WITH LOVE
Give me your hand.
Bear with me.
I'll do it myself.
Is your face okay?
I'm fine.
Sun Yu. Does it hurt?
It's just a scratch. Don't worry.
Put it on.
Thanks.
Sun Yuanzhu.
Please
don't get into a fight again.
You're a smart guy.
Don't fight.
We were just talking,
but then they threatened
to put you two in a gunny sack
if we continued.
So we had to be physical.
It's not worth it.
It is.
It is by fate that the four of us
found each other.
I wasn't there back then,
so I couldn't do much.
Now that they threatened to harm you,
we will step in to protect you.
Guys. It's all my fault.
I will shoulder the responsibilities.
I'll find a place for all of you
as soon as possible.
Are we…
parting ways now?
Unless
I buy this place.
But I don't have money now.
Everything comes to an end eventually.
People come and go.
That's life.
I'll buy you bubble tea next time.
Thanks.
Tao.
- What happened to your face?
- Nothing.
Someone hit you?
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine.
Come.
Tell me. Who hit you?
The real estate agency in my neighborhood.
I see. Send me the address right now.
- I'm fine.
- Look at you now.
How is that fine?
I don't care.
What are you doing?
Hello? Where are you?
Stop eating. Someone hit my best friend.
I'll send you the address later.
You'll come with me.
They bullied my friend.
I'm going to turn their place upside down.
He won't even know what hit him.
Lumi. I'm fine. We called the police.
Their place has been closed down.
It's all in the past now.
You have no idea how scummy
a real estate agency can be.
They intimidate you every day.
They jam your lock.
Listen. When it comes to those jerks,
you deal with them swiftly.
The officer told us to come to them
if anything happened.
Police officers can do it their way.
I can do it my way.
Morning, Luke.
Someone hit you.
I fell.
Come to my office during your lunch break
to report on your work.
What happened?
You fell?
SHANG ZHITAO
Yes.
Fall again.
Let me see how you hit the corner
of your mouth.
I'm impressed.
You landed on your face.
Lumi. What happened
to Shang Zhitao's face?
Hit by the scummy real estate agency.
LUMI
I just found the agency.
CHEN KUANNIAN
Hello?
You reported unethical businesses before,
didn't you?
An illegal agency
contravened laws by committing
verbal assault and physical violence.
I need your help.
We'll check it out together.
Put my name as the plaintiff.
That agency over there.
That one?
It breached the contract
and attacked others.
CHENGJU REAL ESTATE
- I'll ask around.
- Yes, please do.
You can count on me.
We're identifying the person in charge.
Let's wait for a bit.
You reported them in person.
Just who exactly are they?
Do you have any proof?
Check their fire safety regulations.
Then check if they operate
beyond their license.
And then, check their taxes.
Close them down.
Investigate them one by one.
I have time.
You're mad.
Don't show your face.
What if they target you?
This is the place.
I see this agency has a lot of enemies.
Another group of mobs to trash the place.
Hello?
Lumi.
Leave with your underlings now.
I don't want to bail you out
at the police station tomorrow.
Boss. My men are here.
We're not turning back.
They hit my best friend.
I'm avenging Shang Zhitao.
Just leave.
People like them need to be
dealt with lawfully.
Boss. You're intervening personally?
Guys, let's go back first.
Someone will punish them for me.
Let's go.
You know them?
- Mister.
- Yes?
I have made several calls.
And I did ask around.
This agency has a criminal record.
Anyway, you have lodged a report.
It will be handled. Don't worry.
Thank you for the hard work.
All right. See you.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it. Just doing my job.
Boss.
Several men in the agency
are straight-up cowards.
They ganged up on Shang Zhitao
and the rest.
Don't show mercy when your men hit them.
Listen.
She had it coming.
We were fighting, and she rushed in.
She was asking for it.
Also, look at the scratches
on Zeng's hand.
- See?
- Look.
The girl's face was ruined.
Listen. If you don't hit them,
they won't learn their lesson.
But not this harsh.
Those are kids.
Buddy, you must be new here.
A new owner in this neighborhood?
Have a cigarette. Come.
What happened to your hand?
Someone created a scene
at my agency several days ago.
Two girls scratched me.
It's fine.
But then a jerk reported our business.
Right?
It was me.
I…
Stop.
What the heck?
- What are you doing?
- What the heck?
Why did you get into a fight?
They started it first.
- They said they would kill me
- Assault is a crime.
if I didn't withdraw the report.
Trying to be a thug, aren't you?
I'll call the police now.
No.
- He hit us. Look around you.
- He hit us.
This is serious.
They hit you hard.
I'm the one getting hit.
They are leaving now?
This is not over yet.
- Get examined. We'll take your statement.
- I am just…
- I'll head to the hospital with you.
- Enough.
- It's standard procedure.
- I'm fine.
They just left?
It's just a bruise.
Luan Nian.
We've known each other for years.
I didn't know you could be
such a protective boyfriend.
I couldn't believe it myself either.
I must meet her now.
We'll invite Song and Tan Mian.
If you tell anyone about this,
I'll tell your wife about all your exes.
Why are you mad?
Do you have to go this far?
Shang Zhitao.
Come down now. I'm by the entrance.
Do you not have my number?
I do.
Why didn't you tell me
you got into a fight?
Why didn't you tell me you got hit?
Is my phone just for show,
or is your brain just for show?
You're stupid.
And your flatmates are also stupid.
Fight the scummy agency?
Do you think you're a heroine?
That you can defend justice?
Did I say you could speak?
So you don't speak
when I told you not to speak.
Are you this obedient? Speak.
Speak now.
I just thought your time was precious.
And you were always busy.
I didn't want to trouble you
for such a trivial matter.
I can handle it.
So getting evicted and getting hit
is a small matter, Shang Zhitao?
What are we?
At work, we're colleagues.
Outside of work, we're nothing.
Is that it?
But it's not exactly
something to brag about.
It's quite embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
My girlfriend got hit,
and I was the last one to find out.
That sure isn't embarrassing at all.
Shang Zhitao.
Did you ever view me as your boyfriend?
Don't be mad.
You can scold me.
Just drive properly.
Look at your face. It's ruined.
I've asked the doctor.
He said it wouldn't leave a scar.
Now you're worried about scarring.
You deserve a scar.
Stupid.
Does it hurt?
Show me.
It doesn't hurt when you show you care.
Go away.
Who cares about you?
Don't be mad.
What was that?
You…
How did you get hurt?
What happened?
It's none of your business.
You didn't tell me everything,
so I won't tell you either.
Did you…
confront that agency?
They pissed me off.
Does it hurt? Let me see.
Where else did you get hurt?
- It hurts.
- Show me.
My mouth. My face. My leg.
Everywhere hurts.
Shang Zhitao.
What is my number?
I…
Memorize it now.
Don't be mad.
I'll do my best
to memorize your number. Okay?
You don't know my number?
Memorize it now.
One.
Eight.
Seven. Zero.
Eight. Eight. Eight.
Call me first if anything happens.
Do you like it?
I do.
Let me see.
It's so red.
I'm fine. No broken bones.
Does it hurt?
Where are you going to stay now?
I plan to stay here for a few days.
Can I?
How many days?
Five days.
Sure.
Then can I borrow your car tomorrow?
What for?
I need a car to carry my things.
Knowing your driving skills,
I won't let you drive my car.
I'll drive you there.
Tomorrow after work?
Okay.
Oh.
Tomorrow, I have a new flatmate.
A new flatmate?
Closed down?
How come?
I haven't even done anything.
Someone made a report
about their fire safety regulations?
They got hit as well?
Locked up in the police station?
I see.
Our boss just taught those pricks
who hit you a lesson.
Who…
Who?
Luan Nian. Our boss.
He's amazing.
As our boss,
he goes out of his way
to take care of our well-being.
What did I tell you, Shang Zhitao?
Luan Nian treats you differently.
How did you know it was him?
I was there. Then he called me
to ask me to go back.
Tao.
You must thank him this time.
I know. I will thank him properly.
And thank you too, Lumi,
for standing up for me.
But please don't tell anyone about this.
It'll look bad.
What's there to be afraid of? Why?
I need to rush the proposal
regarding the two interns.
Otherwise, I won't be able to go home.
Go then.
Mentoring an intern
is quite challenging at the beginning.
It reminds me of the time
when you mentored me.
It must have been tough on you.
Don't humble yourself.
I taught everyone the same thing.
It's up to them
how they use the knowledge.
And you did so well.
All the best.
Work hard, work more, so that I can chill.
Yes. I work hard. You chill.
LUAN NIAN
See you at the parking lot.
I need to head to a place
to pick up my new flatmate.
PETISM
Luan Nian.
MISSING OWNER
It's still here.
- We're here to check on this dog.
- Sure.
Puppy.
- Hey.
- Puppy.
Give him some water.
- He's so obedient.
- Right?
We put up the notice three months ago,
but no one came to claim him.
We can't keep him in a pet store forever.
Shang Zhitao, why are you so lucky?
You ran into a Samoyed.
It costs several thousand yuan for one.
Do you think I can raise it?
Sure.
I love dogs too.
I love them.
If you want to raise him,
let's do it together.
If Lei and Yuanzhu
are not allergic to fur,
we can bring him home to live with us.
What is your name?
Let's give you a name.
You will be…
Luke. Luke.
What? What's his name?
Luke.
If the Luke at work bullies me,
I'll come back and bully you.
Is this how you do your work?
If you can't do it, just resign.
Bad boy. Luke.
- Sure. I like that name.
- Luke.
You can destress.
Luke.
Does this mean you miss him a lot?
No.
Luke. Luke.
Luke.
I think he likes the name.
Luke, you have a home now.
Let's go home.